[Meet Yourself]
[Episode 01]
This way, please.
Manager Xu.
Good morning.
Morning.
Here's your key card.
Thanks.
Hello.
Check out?
Could you tell me your room number, please?
701. I get it.
Okay.
Lisa.
Find a table for our guest.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
What's your room number?
328.
Okay.
This way, with me.
Helen.
Madam.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Be careful of the shattered glass.
Sure.
I can do it myself.
I see you wearing a short skirt.
Terribly sorry.
My apology.
The executive suites are fully booked
this weekend.
Much as I want to,
I cannot upgrade it for you.
How about this?
I will prepare two meal tickets
as you check in as present.
I will give you an upgrade the next time.
See you tomorrow, Mr. Liu.
[Restroom]
We have more guests during holidays.
The receptionists must stay alert.
Do not miss any
guests as they walk in.
As for the luggage deposit,
double-check the claim tag!
The incident yesterday
must be avoided.
Aunt!
Lingdang!
Let mom have the phone.
I sent you the message the day before.
About what?
She must be too busy.
Let me talk.
Is that mom talking?
You're not in Shanghai. You're back!
Hongdou.
It's your father's birthday today.
You must have forgotten.
Not at all!
I was about to call you!
Dad!
Come over.
Have you eaten?
I'm having it now.
Happy birthday, dad.
How's your stomach?
I told you to see a doctor.
Did you do it?
I'll get a gastroscopy tomorrow.
Nanxing will go with me.
She's there for a color Doppler test.
It's chronic.
Don't worry.
Okay. That makes me relieved.
Nanxing is reliable.
Look at you.
Why Beijing on your own?
You could have worked in Shanghai.
Sure.
How about working as a cleaner
in our company?
How kind of you.
I'd rather not take that job.
I'll be promoted next season
as the associate director of the Rooms Division.
Have fun at the birthday party.
Lingdang.
Kiss me goodbye.
Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Bye.
[I've bought dad a leather coat.
Buy him a new shaver or whatever instead.]
Hongdou.
Why didn't you reply to my message?
I didn't get to!
The hot and sour soup today tastes great.
I get you some.
What do you want from me?
Just a small favor.
My friend's younger sister.
She's an intern at the reception.
Hi.
She's capable.
Please guide her.
Manager Xu, I'm Li Meiyu.
Hi.
Hello.
Will you graduate this year?
Are you free after work?
I want to treat you to dinner.
No. I need to walk my dog.
You have a dog!
What about tomorrow for lunch?
I have a day off tomorrow, remember?
Sorry.
It's a very important client.
I need to go.
Enjoy your meal.
Li Meiyu.
Two tips for you.
First,
do not eat spring onion or garlic at work.
Second, don't drink too much water.
Time to go.
Hongdou!
What's wrong?
My back hurts.
You'll take a gastroscopy tomorrow.
Can you eat now?
Yeah.
Fasting for solids and liquids after 10.
What do you want?
Pizza!
Sure.
You've lost weight.
Really?
Are you on a diet?
Not at all.
It must be the business trip.
I went away for four days last week.
I visited two hotels,
investigated their environments
and recreational facilities.
I finished a report of 20,000 words.
Can you imagine?
There's more, Li Jing, our classmate,
commented below my post
saying I envy you! Travel at public expense!
Shall we watch TV while eating?
If you like.
Your affluent sister
sent you a lot of cubilose!
That was last year.
Xu Hongdou!
It expired six months ago!
So is the chili sauce!
I had it with noodles yesterday.
Is that the nourishment from my mom?
Yeah, I'd take that occasionally.
What's wrong?
Look at it yourself!
It's gone moldy!
I put that in the fridge the
last time you gave it to me.
It's only been a while.
The last time I visited
you was half a year ago.
That long?
Yeah.
We're like the cowherd and the weaver fairy.
Meeting twice a year
even though we both live in Beijing.
I'll help you clean your fridge after dinner.
We work so hard to make money.
But what for?
For a car!
You applied for the plate lottery.
I'll never win it.
Take it easy.
Even if you bought one,
there's the even-odd license plate policy.
And there are rush hours
So hard to find a parking spot.
I used to think well,
I can't afford a house here.
I'll get a car instead.
What about now?
Even that is beyond me.
Forget about it.
Remember last spring festival?
You drove a car into a
tree in your hometown.
Come on.
Let's move on.
But that's the truth.
Don't drink.
It's bad for your stomach.
It doesn't hurt.
This one is yours.
Delicious.
I'm having bags under my eyes.
I'm used to mine.
I've got dark circles and crow's feet, too.
Staying up late and there you go.
Speaking of that,
I'm afraid of getting old.
It's time to find a boyfriend.
Go for it.
You talked about
your new colleague.
He's your type, right?
From an affluent family.
And he looks cute.
What's he called?
Sun Zhixin.
But he's six years younger than me.
I'm afraid even if we date,
it won't last for long.
I don't want a fruitless relationship.
See that?
So typical of you.
Listen to yourself.
Always talking.
But the age gap could be a problem.
What about you?
Any new suitor?
Yeah, a colleague.
Not going to work.
What's wrong?
Your ex-boyfriend, Mr. Corgi.
You broke up because
you live too far apart.
One in Yanjiao,
and the other in East Fourth Ring.
You met each other
less than once a week.
[We can hardly meet.
Why don't we just break up?]
[Okay.]
That's to say,
being too far away doesn't work.
Greeting every day is annoying.
He's just a colleague.
I can't feel the thing.
Living a hard life.
I want to retire.
Look at me.
No house, no car, no boyfriend.
I feel lost.
How's that so?
You have your goals.
Buy a house, buy a car, get a boyfriend.
Then?
Then you'll be happy.
For real?
I hope so.
Forget about it.
That's too surreal.
How about we
take annual leaves
and take a trip to Yunnan?
I can't, I'm afraid.
I'll soon be promoted.
It must be busy.
Look at you.
That's annoying!
You came up with the plan.
You've always been busy.
It's the third year you stand me up.
My apology.
I... I promise, next year!
You've got no reputation now.
How about I give you a
great birthday present?
I got a pay raise!
I want a handbag.
You have it!
I'm turning off the lamp.
My back hurts.
Scratch it for me.
Sure.
Right there.
[Happiness is the meaning and the purpose of life,
the whole aim and end of human existence. Aristotle]
Hongdou?
What's wrong? Having a stomachache?
I had some gel on my belly
when taking the Doppler test.
It feels weird.
Feeling itchy?
Nope.
Are you allergic to it?
I have no idea.
Feel anything?
Xu Hongdou!
Room No. 2.
Well.
Come on, I'll wait here.
Come on.
Is she your relative?
According to the result,
the size of the head of the pancreas is abnormal.
What's that?
The head of the pancreas, here.
I suggest
you register at the surgery
department and take a CT scan.
I'm afraid it's acute.
[CT Examination Room 2]
Chen Nanxing.
It's your turn.
It's on your right side.
Thanks.
Chen Nanxing.
Here are your results.
Come in.
Conservative treatment?
Not taking surgery?
Advanced pancreatic cancer.
It has spread.
She can only take conservative treatment.
To ease her pain.
But she's so young.
How could that be?
She's the only child of her family.
I can't believe it.
Thankfully,
your examination results are okay.
I didn't hear you
clearly on the phone.
I thought it was you.
My heart stopped when I heard...
Mom.
Well.
I'm having dinner now.
Dishes get cold.
Carry on.
That's it. Bye-bye.
[We sincerely apologize for the inconvenience.
Xu Hongdou, Waldorf Hotel.]
It hurts.
Kangkang.
Does your mom know you're here?
She's having dinner.
She asks me to stay here with Nanxing.
Good.
Taking care of her.
Got a message from work.
That hurts.
I knew it.
You have to work
until you're dead.
Come on.
Take care of yourself, alright?
The misery never ends. Why not quit it?
Don't say that right here.
You know what I mean.
I'll quit.
My hands hurt.
You hit me so hard. Let's try another one.
How about... rock,
scissors, paper?
Sure!
Rock, scissors, paper.
Rock.
Mom!
Are you okay, mom?
Kangkang, look away!
Doctor!
Nurse!
There, there. I'm with you.
Hongdou.
Mom!
I want some oden.
Mom...
A few more eggs.
Sure.
Eggs.
There.
I want that one.
Soup. More soup, please.
It reminds me of our days in college.
I'd always get hungry
when the lights were out.
And I'd ask you to buy
spicy hot pot for me.
Yeah,
the restaurant went bankrupt in the end.
No, they didn't!
They made enough money and
bought a house in their hometown.
Their kids were in middle school.
They went back to take care of the kid.
Really?
Of course!
They told me!
So good at small talk.
You're way too busy.
Right now,
you should live a happy life!
Eat well, drink well.
Talk to others.
Exchange thoughts.
Make friends.
The money we make. What's that for?
A better life.
I used to tell myself
to get a boyfriend soon,
get married and have a baby.
I'm afraid I'd be
lonely when I'm old.
Now I see.
That was nothing.
I never knew what I really want.
You want happiness.
For me right now?
Health is happiness.
Do you remember our classmate,
Li Ruiyuan?
She has two babies already.
For real?
Two babies already?
I have no idea!
Look at me.
I don't have any.
Yeah, you're still single.
Why are you so mean?
Take turnip.
Turnip tastes good!
It's okay.
[Symposium on Asian Biotechnology and Medicine]
1603 is not ready. What do you mean?
A smell of hot pot?
Try air freshener spray.
Executive Suites are overbooked today.
Okay.
Thanks, Hongdou.
Excuse me.
What's up?
That's loud!
Manager Xu!
Over here.
Sorry.
It doesn't match.
[Nanxing's mom]
Hold on a second.
Hello?
I'm on my way.
Ask for leave for me.
Manager Xu?
You have problems with your stomach.
You should eat slowly.
I know you're busy. Still, eat well.
You need balanced nutrition.
Sir.
You lost a gear.
It's grinding.
It's been working for too long. Worn out now.
The clock would be inaccurate with it.
I'm swapping it with a new one.
You may leave
after taking the IV.
Doctor, am I dying?
I've given you an examination.
You're fine.
You fainted.
It's not as concerning as it looks.
You had temporary ischemia and hypoxia
due to excessive pressure or panic.
Just relax.
Try not to be anxious.
I thought I was sick.
You suffer from
anemia and malnutrition.
You need iron supplementation.
Be sure to eat on time.
Have more eggs and meat.
Don't skip meals just for losing weight.
Thank you.
No problem.
You're free to go
after taking the IV.
Okay.
Manager Xu.
I've paid the bills.
I'll lay the test report here.
Okay.
Thank you.
Well.
I have an emergency.
It's my boyfriend's birthday.
He takes a flight here from Guangzhou.
Go for him. I'm fine.
I...
I should wait till the IV is over.
I'm feeling alright.
Just go.
He must be waiting.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Manager Xu.
Call me immediately
if you need anything.
See you tomorrow.
Hongdou.
I don't know how to put this
in front of you.
I guess I have to talk to you
over voice messages.
Maybe you don't get the chance to reply.
Maybe this is my last word.
When I'm gone,
my parents would suffer the most.
Please give them a call
during festivals.
Talk to them for me.
A call is enough.
No need for anything else.
I know about them.
They never ask others for a favor.
I'm sure they'd be
glad to hear from you.
When I'm gone,
don't be sad for too long.
Cry it out.
Let it out.
That's enough.
You know about me.
I didn't do evil things.
Right?
I'll go to a great place after death.
Don't worry.
Besides,
I won't be painful by that time.
I'm freed.
You should be happy for me.
Don't you think?
I regret
not confessing to Sun Zhixin.
The earlier I make my move,
the sooner the romance arrives.
Right?
Right now,
much as I want,
I can't witness the world away from here.
But you can witness it for me.
I want to eat,
to drink,
to play.
The things I wanted to try,
I left them to you.
To eat, to drink, to play.
But there's one thing.
Be sure to check the
expiration date before you eat.
You'd always leave
them in the fridge
and forget about them.
What's more,
be sure to eat well,
sleep well.
Live a good life.
Must be happy.
Must go out
and open your mind to others.
Make some friends.
All in all,
there has to be someone
to take up my place.
Right?
When seeing someone you like,
take the initiative. Go after him.
I know you are good-looking.
But you can't just sit there and wait.
Have a relationship.
Seize the day.
That's my assignment for you.
Do you hear me?
When I'm gone,
be sure to be happy for me.
Live a good life for me.
Stop wasting your time.
Take care.
Live your life the way you want.
I will bless you for sure.
But on one condition.
Be sure to burn paper money for me.
The more the better.
I'm tired.
So much for now.
That's a separate line for my last word.
I'll make amendments
when I think of something new.
By the way,
thankfully, I didn't confess to Sun Zhixin.
Or I'd be a drag.
Alright. That's all.
Enough talking.
I'm out.
I'm feeling
great today.
I could live for another 500 years.
Can you believe that?
Will you drop by after work today?
I want some lazy dragon rolls.
Buy me some, please.
♫ Listen to the rain
falling into the silent forest ♫
♫ Enjoy the mountainous landscape at sunset ♫
♫ The raindrops on the roof
fall into the eyes secretly ♫
♫ The world is like a quiet island ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises,
the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ Go to a windy place to meet you ♫
[Letter of Resignation]
Yeah, mom.
I got three months of paid leave.
I haven't taken any vacation for years.
I won't go home now.
I want to spend a few months in Yunnan.
Take a break.
I want to travel.
♫ Listen to the rain
falling into the silent forest ♫
♫ Enjoy the mountainous landscape at sunset ♫
♫ The raindrops on the roof
fall into the eyes secretly ♫
♫ The world is like a quiet island ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises,
the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises,
the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ Go to a windy place to meet you ♫